# Devdeepsinh Ashoksinh Jadeja

🗣 Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India 🛮 devdeepjadeja2001@gmail.com 🔲 +91 9512373391 📊 in/devdeepsinh-jadeja-0591

devdeepsinh0591.github.io/Portfolio-Devdeepsinh-Jadeja/

#### **SUMMARY**

A self-motivated IT developer with 2.5+ years of professional experience in software analysis, design, and development using Microsoft ASP.NET Domain. Capable of developing both client and server portions of large & small scales applications. significantly expediting project timelines while maintaining rigorous quality standards. Giving my best to Organizations with 100% effort.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Junior Software Engineer**

**Qeleo Technolabs** 

January 2022 - Present, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Qeleo TechnoLabs offers IT services, focusing on mobile tech for retail, eCommerce, and enterprise mobility.

- Developed custom applications using the .NET framework for increased functionality and enhanced the user experience within the organizations.
- Contributed to the development of scalable and maintainable.NET applications using: C# & ASP.NET Core/MVC, JavaScript/jQuery, Ajax, CSS/Bootstrap and SQL Server, Web API/REST.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to desiagn & develop, appealing and user-friendly interfaces that facilitated seamless navigation for end-users.
- Increased system stability through rigorous debugging and troubleshooting of complex issues within the .NET framework.
- Developed reusable code libraries/components that expedited development time for future projects by providing ready-to-use resources.
- Conducted thorough testing to identify bugs and ensure optimal functionality before deploying web applications into production environments.
- Contributed to innovative solutions with thoughtful problem-solving techniques & completed products within the project deadline.
- Utilized modern front-end frameworks such as React or Angular to create modular, scalable UI components

#### Web Developer Intern

InfoLabz IT Services Pvt. Ltd

May 2021 - July 2021, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Wrote custom HTML and JavaScript for existing websites.
- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Developed interactive prototypes using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery for client presentations and feedback sessions.
- Studied user requirements to gain a strong understanding of project initiatives and deadlines.
- Followed best practices for software development and web security

# **PROJECTS**

## **Educstion Resources Management System**

eduresource.ml/ • January 2021 - March 2021

- Features: The product enables direct resource sharing between both end users and organizations with their own dashboard support, & it ensures the supply of all educational resources on timely, cost-free, and commission-free access without third-party involvement.
- Github:- https://github.com/Devdeepsinh0591/Education-Resource-Sharing-System
- Category:- Personal
- Engineered a comprehensive Education Resources Management System using the .NET framework, facilitating seamless resource sharing with integrated APIs and reusable plugins, enhancing accessibility for educational organizations.

#### **Portfolio Website**

devdeepsinh0591.github.io/Portfolio-Devdeepsinh- Jadeja/ • May 2021 - July 2021

- Features:- It's a Personal Portfolio website with all the required information.
- $\bullet \ Git Hub: \ https://github.com/Devdeepsinh0591/Portfolio-\ Devdeepsinh-Jadeja/$
- Category:- Personal
- Engineered a dynamic portfolio website utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery, Ajax, and MySQL that showcased professional achievements and skills, with integrated APIs to enhance visitor interaction and data retrieval efficiency.

#### **Covid Cases Tracker**

GIT Institute ORG Project

- GitHub:- https://github.com/Devdeepsinh0591/Covid-cases-tracker
- Features:- Engineered an automated Covid Cases Tracker web app utilizing React that delivered real-time state-wise Covid statistics in India, resulting in a 40% increase in user engagement and enhancing public information access through intuitive data visualization.

# **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor Of Engineering**

Minor in Computer Engineering • Gujarat Technological University • Ahmedabad, Gujarat • 2022 • CGPA:- 8.06

• Graduation with Distinction

### **High School**

Minor in Mathematics • Gujarat Secondary & Higher Secondary Education Board • Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India • 2018

# **SKILLS**

Software: Asp.Net, .NET Core, MVC, Webforms, Linq, Ado.Net, Ajax, Wpf/Wcf, Entity Framework, MicroServicies, Web API, REST/Soap.

Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, C#, Java(basics).

**Database**:- SQL Server/MySQL. **SQL**- Tsql, SP, SSRS/SSMS.

Version Control:- Visual Studio, Git, Github.

**Other**:- Team Collaboration, Interpersonal Communication.